annaslinens.com 2015-03-21

# Privacy Policy

Anna’s Linens, Inc.  (“Anna’s Linens”) respects our customers’ privacy. We collect information about our customers in our stores and through our website in an effort to always improve our services and enhance customers’ shopping experience. We also use this information so that we may communicate with our customers to advise them of special offers, promotions, products, and services.  

In providing Anna’s Linens with personal information, you consent to the manner in which your information is collected, disclosed, used and protected and how Anna’s Linens also manages the information. Although most changes to the Privacy Agreement are likely to be minor, Anna’s Linens may change its privacy policy from time to time, and in Anna’s Linens, Inc.’s sole discretion.  Please review our privacy policy on a regular basis to make sure you have read the latest version and you understand what we do with your personal information. Your continued use of our services or our website following the posting of changes to these terms means that you consent to those changes.

If you have any questions about our privacy policy, please [click here](http://www.annaslinens.com/contact-us?utm_campaign=footer_contact_us "Contact Us") to contact us. 

**Type of Information Collected.   **Personal information may include such things as:  your name, email address, postal address, phone number, gender, birthday, personal interests, etc., when you visit our website, or store, or if you place an order with us online or by phone, save your information with us online, call us, or otherwise contact us to ask a question or concern, or if you make a purchase, or participate in a promotion, program, or customer related survey. We maintain a record of your product interests and the purchases you make online or by phone or in any of our stores. We may combine all of this information with information about you that we acquire from our joint marketing partners and from unrelated third parties.

To protect children, Anna’s Linens will never knowingly request or collect personally identifiable information online from anyone under the age of thirteen without prior verifiable parental consent. Our website is a “general audience site” and is not targeted to or intended for use by children. 

**Use of Information.** Examples of how Anna’s Linens may use this information includes:  
  • Completing orders and providing customers with updates on the status of the shipping of orders order via email.   
  • Sending communications to customers about services, products, promotions, and programs.   
  • Assisting Anna’s Linens in learning about shopping preferences and interests and feedback on promotions.  
  • Enabling use to address issues and improve our services, products and website.   
  • Protecting security of our website and business operations.  
  • Use in analyzing shopping data and trends.

Customers always may opt out of being contacted.

**Sharing Customer Information**

Customer information may be shared with Anna’s Linens’ employees, independent contractors, agents or other related and unrelated Anna’s Linens businesses and/or business partners acting on our behalf. This includes when Anna’s Linens works with other companies in providing related services, products and promotions.  Anna’s Linens may also provide information as legally required, or when Anna’s Linens believes in good faith that disclosure is reasonably **** necessary to protect the property or rights of Anna’s Linens, third parties or the public at large. Anna’s Linens does not share or sell its customer lists, data and personal information to third-parties for solicitation purposes.

Other related programs including “loyalty” programs, may require us to provide customer information to third-parties, including credit card processor information to a third-party administering such program.

Also, if there is a transfer of all, or substantially all of Anna’s Linens, Inc.’s assets, were acquired, user information would be one of the assets that is transferred or acquired by a third party.

**Access of Information.   **Customers may review and change certain personal information, such as name and contact information. To access information on Anna’s Linens website, a customer may sign into the email account and using the email address and password to edit such information.

A customer may also contact us directly by [clicking here](http://www.annaslinens.com/contact-us?utm_campaign=footer_contact_us "Contact Us"). 

**Opting out of Contact.   **If you, as a customer of Anna’s Linens, rather not receive communications from us as to sales events, promotional items, and other specials, simply provide Anna’s Linens with your full name and the email address used when registering with Anna’s Linens or follow the unsubscribe process as outlined within the email communication from Anna’s Linens.   Upon your request not be contacted, your name will be included in a “do not contact file” to ensure that your request is honored.  It may take up to ten to fifteen business days to process a request.During such time, customers may continue receiving communications from Anna’s Linens. Customers may continue to receive Anna’s Linens’ communications as to promotional and sales specials by logging into the website account and changing preferences, or, for our “loyalty” program, by signing up with Anna’s Linens by visiting one of our stores.

Please note that when you make an online purchase from us, we will continue to confirm your order status and shipment by email. We may also need to contact you via telephone, email or postal mail with questions or information regarding your order. **      
 **

**Cookies.   **In short, “cookies” are small data files that are stored on your computer when you visit a website. Anna’s Linens uses cookies. Cookies enable Anna’s Linens customers to shop via the website and are also used to better enhance the online shopping and browsing experience of our customers. Cookies also allow Anna’s Linens to collect information for such things as “loyalty” programs, and tracking orders, and customer preferences.

A customer may set her or his computer browser not to accept cookies or to notify you when you are sent cookies. 

**Security.   **Anna’s Linens takes reasonable steps to protect personal information.  However, no e-commerce solution, website, database or system is completely secure or “hacker proof”.   

**"Phishing".** "Phishing" is a scam designed to steal your personal information. If you receive an email that looks like it is from us asking you for your personal information, do not respond. We will never request your password, user name, credit card information, or other personal information through email.

**Contact.** Anna’s Linens may be contacted by [clicking here](http://www.annaslinens.com/contact-us?utm_campaign=footer_contact_us "Contact Us") as to any questions on: this privacy policy, updating personal information, or making a choice as to receiving promotional communications.

**California Privacy Rights.    **California Civil Code Section 1798.83 permits customers of Anna’s Linens, Inc. who are California residents to request certain information regarding our disclosure of personal information to third parties for their direct marketing purposes. To make such a request, please write to us at the above address with the attention to Anna’s Linens (California Privacy Rights).
